[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
[narrator]
With the death of King Meruem,
the battle between Chimera Ants
and humans was finally over.
The Republic of East Gorteau and the NGL
were placed under the provisional rule
of the International Security Agency,
effectively dismantling both countries.
The Mitene Union's
three remaining countries
divided East Gorteau's assets equally,
and after brief negotiations, agreed
to have joint control over the territory.
As for the NGL,
there was a proposal to permanently
designate all uninhabited land
as a nature reserve, in hopes
that this would prevent future conflict,
and it was quickly approved
in the international assembly.
It was also agreed that the nature reserve
would be placed under the jurisdiction
of the Hunter Association.
[Welfin] You sure about this?
[Bloster] You bet!
I'm gonna live right here, no question!
I don't remember Gyro, but still,
this place just feels like home.
and didn't work for Gyro.
[Welfin] Well, I'm not gonna
twist your arm.
This is probably safer
than the other countries.
No doubt about that.
Just one good look at me, and the
peacekeepers would arrest me on the spot.
Hmm? What are you talking about?
Hey! Are you done? Let's get moving.
She's such a brat.
Just give me a minute!
those like you and Hina, who do remember,
you all seem a little,
I don't know… different.
Maybe it's the light in your eyes,
how you look off into the distance.
I can tell just by looking at you, like,
"Yeah, this guy remembers his past."
It's that she's not able to.
She's probably a little kid.
We might not see each other again.
So, take care, okay?
I will.
Just don't die… until you're dead.
That's always been my favorite phrase.
[Welfin] Oh! Right!
[Bloster] So it's like
"seize the day," huh?
-[Welfin] Huh. Later!
-[Bloster] Yeah!
[wind blowing]
[Hina humming]
-Wait, do I know them? Guess not.
-Huh?
[chuckles] No point in thinking
about the dead, right?
Keep looking forward! Full speed ahead!
Are you positive we can make it safely
to the harbor?
Yes. It's a government vehicle, so
I'll show my card and they'll let us pass.
[sighs] Before long,
I'll be living in Meteor City.
[gulps]
[sighs]
Just a little bit longer to go.
And you know what that means,
that we're gonna be back on top
in no time at all!
Yay!
[Hina chuckles]
Well, I envy your unbridled optimism.
I just wish that I shared it.
"Optimism"? Got that right!
-[Hina giggles]
-[tires screech]
[Bizeff] Knock it off!
Might as well enjoy… whatever is next.
[Welfin] Yeah, that's the spirit!
in the hopes of finding Gyro.
[gasps]
[doors slam]
[Bloster sighs] Well, I can't blame 'em.
Hey! People of the NGL,
I promise, we mean you no harm!
I've got something I need to ask you!
All right!
Sounds like you speak our language.
Tell us who you are.
Uh, well…
You're the only ones I can turn to.
[mellow music playing]
[imperceptible]
[gasps]
[sobbing]
Reina?
How did…
How did you know?
Reina! Reina!
[thud]
[sobbing]
[Shidore] How could you tell it was me?
[mother] I'm your mother, Reina!
Of course, I could tell! How could I not?
[both sobbing]
He told the monster to go away,
and he told me to run.
He kept me safe!
If it hadn't been for him…
I'm the one who's sorry.
Sorry I wasn't there with you,
sorry I couldn't keep you safe.
Reina dear, welcome back home!
Why don't we all go eat together?
-[woman] Hello!
-[gasps]
Would you like to stay and join us?
We want to thank you for what you've done.
[Bloster] Look, I'm not that kinda guy,
okay? See ya!
Damn it! Now we're even. It's over.
Damn that stupid octopus!
He never should've let me live!
[dramatic music playing]
[Shidore] Thank you!
Come on.
What is this? Why am I crying?
[narrator] Reina and Bloster,
home at last.
Look like the politicians have somehow
turned this into an international crisis.
[Colt] Is that right?
Just act the part of a good Magical Beast
and there won't be a problem.
She keeps saying her name's not Reina.
Okay, what is it, then?
For the last time, my name is not Reina!
All right?
So stop it. Don't call me that.
My name is Kite!
[intense music playing]
Gon! [grunts] Killua!
Normally, I would recommend
that he be transported to a specialist.
But until he can be taken off
life support, it's too risky.
I see. Then we'll just have to bring
the specialist to us.
Considering his heroism,
he deserves at least that much.
I'll cover all of the expenses.
If necessary,
we'll rebuild the whole hospital.
But know this,
we are never going to let Gon die.
I wish you'd said,
"Let's get him together."
Let's go.
[Killua] When you said that, were you
ordering me as your teammate?
Or were you telling me as your friend?
I know. I'm just sulking.
But this time,
I won't let you off the hook.
You'd better apologize!
I'm going to make you better.
You hear me?
I swear!
I'm gonna make you apologize!
So, I'm assembling specialists.
I'll use Hide and Seek to transport
the equipment and the medical staff.
I'm going to save Gon.
[gasps]
Go ahead and get the doctors,
because he's gonna need 'em…
right up until I get back.
[Knov] Killua?
[static crackling]
[tape rattles]
Uh, my name is Netero.
I'm resigning as chairman,
so please take care.
If you don't reach a 95% quorum,
then call for a revote.
I'd say it's a level-D difficulty.
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Debate Among Zodiacs."
I won't say anything
until I've seen your face.
[Killua] I'm going to make you better.
I swear! I'll make you apologize!
[singer singing in Japanese]